It's Everyone's Turn For Seconds
Critters 2 is a comedy, horror, science fiction film directed by Mick Garris.
Three bounty hunters from space fly back to the town of Grovers Bend, hoping
to save local residents from a new batch of Critter eggs.
Brad, played by Scott Grimes.
Megan, played by Liane Curtis.
Charlie, played by Don Keith Opper.
Harv, played by Barry Corbin.
Wesley, played by Tom Hodges.
Mr. Morgan, played by Sam Anderson.
Critters 2: The Main Course (also known as Critters 2) is a 1988 American science fiction comedy horror film
directed by Mick Garris in his directorial debut, and the second installment in the Critters franchise.
A direct sequel to Critters, the film was written by David Twohy and Garris, and stars
Scott Grimes, Don Keith Opper and Terrence Mann reprising their roles.
The plot takes place two years after the first film, as a batch of planted Critter eggs
begin to hatch and resume their carnivorous appetite upon the town once again.
Although it did not gross as much as the original, the sequel grossed $3.8
million during its theatrical run in the United States.
It is the last installment in the series to be released
theatrically and is followed by Critters 3 in 1991.
The film explores themes of spacecraft, small town,
bounty hunter, hamburger, kansas, usa.
The tone is lighthearted and dark and thought_provoking.